<Document>
  # Hitman

  <Box>
    [color=#999999][italic]"Mission Started."[/italic][/color]
  </Box>

   You're a [color=yellow]Criminal[/color], who takes money to kill people. [color=cyan]Your client wants you to kill them in a very particular way.[/color] Pay attention to your conditions.

    ##Teach your target a lesson
    Your client wants that your client dies once [color=red][italic]by your hand following their specifications.[/italic][/color]
    - [bold]They need not stay dead. Your client only cares that they die once, not for how long they are dead.[/bold]
    - [bold]This is your one task, take the time needed to plan it out.[/bold]


    ##Nice death
    Your client wants you to be respectful to your target. Try to be nice and courteous to them even as you kill them.
    - Interrupting your target well they are doing something is rather rude.
    - Killing someone without even telling them you will or giving them time to talk is also very rude.

    ##Kill them dramatically
    Your client wants to make their death a performance. Give it the show it deserves.
    - You may need to interact with your target socially to set up the correct narrative tension, but remember you need a reason to be talking with them to not seem suspicious.
    - The best tragedies involve a fault of their victims. Knowing what kind of person your target is could help.

    ##Kill them in a funny way
    Your client wants to make their death a joke. Make their death funny.
    - Absurd methods of death are funny. Look into what doesn't seem like it could kill but can.
    - The station and clown has a lot of silly items. Searching maintenance tunnels and the clown's room may get you something useful.

    ##Kill them cleanly
    Your client does not want this death making a mess. Try to do as little damage to the person as you can.
    - Any forms of damage which are internal will be very useful here.
    - Many smaller wounds will look more messy than 1 or 2 big wounds.
    - Death via fire will likely be very messy.

    ##Make their death look like a accident
    Your client would rather others not realize your targets death was a assassination. Try to frame it as a accident.
    - Using or faking regular dangers in their department can go a long way towards making people believe you.
    - If the body does not get reported as suspicious then its unlikely anyone will question it further.

    ##Kill them indirectly
    Your client wants you to take no chances with getting spotted near the body. Try to find a way to kill them indirectly.
    - The remote signaller can be very useful for setting up traps or timing kills.
    - Having a method to tell your target's location will likely be very useful in telling when a trap could be sprung.

    ##Draw-out the kill
    Your client would like that your target suffers as they die. Your client requests you draw out their death.
    - Healing supplies could be useful in ensuring they survive longer than usual.
    - By the nature of this, you likely want to make your method quiet or kill them in a place no one will look for them.

    ##Kill them in a public space
    Your client would like to send a message. Kill your target in public, in front of as many witnesses as you can.
    - Having a method to hide your idenity will be very useful when you need to do this in front of witnesses.
    - Using something to cause panic can be useful in giving you an opening.

    ##Inform them, your target, about the assassination long before it happens
    Your client wants your target to know what's gonna happen to them. Inform your target about their inevitable demise [color=red][bold]long before it happens.[/bold][/color].
    - Doing this will almost always put you under suspicion. Find a method to hide your identity or inform them indirectly.
    - Doing this early on could make your target grow compliant.

    ##Kill someone close to them and make sure they know
    Your client wants your target to be broken mentally and physically. Find someone close to your target and kill them once. Make sure your target knows about their friend's death.
    - The person you kill has to be found out to be dead by your target. This cannot be a silent or permanent kill.
    - You'll need to interact with and stalk your target to figure out who is close to them.
    - There's no modifiers on killing the person close to them.

    ##Gain their trust
    Your client wants your target to feel betrayed when you kill them. Spend a lot of time hanging out with them.
    - You will likely need to get into the same department as your target.
</Document>
